A Guide to the Anson-Greene-Gravely Family Papers, 1832-1999
Library of Virginia
- Ledgers, 5 volumes.
  The ledgers relate to the law practices of George L. Gravely and George D. Gravely. Ledger A, 1894-1899, contains accounts of George D. Gravely & Sons. Ledger B, 1886-1899, contains accounts for George L. Gravely & Sons. Ledger C, 1899-1928, includes accounts for George L. Gravely acting as receiver, special commissioner, and trustee. Ledger D, 1916-1929, includes cash and expense accounts, and information on an account with First National Bank of Martinsville. Ledger E, 1922-1928, contains cash and expense accounts for Gravely & Carter, as well as law practice and First National Bank accounts.